Okay, our XML's looking pretty slick, but
حسنًا، الآن يبدو إكس إم إل أمر سهل،
we still have to add the interactivity with Java.
ولكن لا يزال علينا إضافة التفاعل مع جافا.
Now, using the previous exercises as an example,
الآن، باستخدام التمارين السابقة على أنها مثال،
you're going to make the right side update for team_b.
ستقوم الآن بتحديث الجانب اليمين لـ team_b.
Before doing anything else you're going to copy and paste the code for
قبل فعل أي شيء آخر، ستقوم بنسخ الكود ولصقه لعرض الفريق B
displayForTeamB from the instructor notes into your own code.
من ملاحظات المعلم في الكود الخاص بك.
And you're going to update the text view ID for
وستقوم الآن بتحديث معرف واجهة النص
Team B to team_b_score, if you haven't already.
للفريق B إلى team_b_score، إذا لم تقم بذلك بالفعل.
I'll show you how to do both of these now.
سأوضح لك كيفية فعل كل منهما لهذه الآن.
All right, here we are in our Java code.
حسنًا، نحن الآن في كود جافا.
I've got the display for Team B code copied, I'm going to do this right
لقد عرضت كود الفريق B المنسوخ، سأفعل ذلك الآن أدناه
below, not inside but below, the displayForTeamA and paste.
ليس بالداخل ولكن بالأسفل، عرض الفريق A ولصق المنسوخ.
To make it not inside,
ولجعله ليس في الداخل،
you want to make sure that it's after this bracket right here.
عليك أن تتأكد من أنه بعد هذا القوس هنا.
And you know that the two curly braces match up because when you put your
تعلم أن القوسين المعقوصين متطابقان وذلك لأنه عند وضع المؤشر إلى جانب أحد الأقواس،
cursor next to one of the curly braces, the other one highlights.
يبرز القوس الآخر.
Okay, so I've pasted this code here, good.
حسنًا، ولذلك لقد لصقت هذا الكود هنا، حسنًا.
Now I need to go over to my XML code, get rid of the preview, okay.
والآن أريد الانتقال إلى كود إكس إم إل، سأخرج من المعاينة، حسنًا.
And I'm going to scroll down to this TextView here, and
سأقوم بالتمرير لأسفل إلى واجهة النص هذه هنا،
I actually already updated this in the last video, but if you need to update
وبقد قمت بتحديثها في الفيديو الأخير، ولكن إذا كنت تريد التحديث،
it, I'm going to pretend I didn't, you could type id and set the id attribute.
فيمكنك كتابة المعرف وضبط خاصية المعرف.
And remember, you want the @+id/ and then you type the id that you want,
وتذكر أنك تريد @+id/ وبعد ذلك يمكنك كتابة المعرف الذي تريده،
in my case, I want team_b_score, okay, cool.
في هذه الحالة، أريد team_b_score، رائع.
Okay, and now you're pretty much ready to start hooking up the Java.
حسنًا، والآن أنت جاهز إلى حد كبير لبدء العمل مع جافا.
I'm not going to give you too, too many instructions, but,
لن أقدم لك العديد من التعليمات،
if you're feeling like you might get stuck, here's some things to consider.
ولكن إذا كنت تشعر بأن هناك بعض الغموض، تجد هنا بعض الأشياء التي يجب وضعها في الاعتبار.
Think about how you're going to associate the buttons
فكر في كيفية ربط الأزرار
with running some code in, Java.
مع بعض الأكواد قيد التشغيل في جافا.
This was one of the first steps we did for the team a side.
كانت هذه إحدى الخطوات الأولى التي قمنا بها للفريق A.
Next, consider hat new variable or variables you'll need.
وبعد ذلك، ضع في اعتبارك المتغير أو المتغيرات الجديدة التي ستحتاج إليها.
Hint, you're going to need at least one.
نصيحة، أنت في حاجة إلى واحد على الأقل.
Finally, think a little bit about what's going to happen when you click
وأخيرًا، فكر قليلًا فيما سيحدث عند النقر
on each button.
فوق كل زر.
Now, I just want to point out that these steps
والآن، فقط أريد الإشارة إلى هذه الخطوات
loosely relate to the steps we used to make the team a side.
والمرتبطة بالخطوات التي استخدمناها لإنشاء الفريق A.
So if you're feeling really, really stuck,
ولذا إذا كنت تشعر بالفعل ببعض الغموض،
reviewing those videos again might be helpful, and then, once you're done,
كرر مشاهدة مقاطع الفيديو ربما تجد بها فائدة، وبمجرد الانتهاء من ذلك،
you have the satisfaction of checking off this box, okay, get to it.
سترضى بوضع علامة على هذا المربع، حسنًا، ضع علامة هنا.